# ISABEL HANKES

2123 Esquire Dr Anchorage, AK 99517

T 605.389.2630

isabel.hankes@gmail.com izthebest.github.io

Profile

Homeschooled Junior passionate about computer science. Girls Who Code alumni and knowledgable in various computer programming languages. Experience teaching and assisting programmers at the Z J Loussac Library Free Code Camp. Member of FPCS Student Government, representing the school in district meetings and statewide legislation, as well as promote respect, love, and professionalism.

Experience

#### Family Partnership Charter School I Library Aide

October 2016 - Present I Anchorage, AK

- Organize FPCS's collection of textbooks, curriculums, supplementary reading resources, fictional books, and media
- Assist students, parents, and teachers to easily find homeschool materials

#### Girls Who Code Summer Immersion Program | Student

July 2016 - August 2016 | Seattle, WA

- Experimented with Scratch, Python, Arduino Robots, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, APIs, mongoDB, nodeJS, and jade
- Strengthened leadership and teamwork skills while working on a final project;
  created a social connectivity platform to support and connect teenagers struggling with mental illnesses such as depression or anxiety

### Military Youth Leadership Summit | Participant June 2016 | Eglin AFB, FL

• Developed leadership skills while competing in team building exercises

## Hickam Air Force Base Commissary | Bagger

October 2015 - April 2016 | Honolulu, HI

Provided quality bagging service to veterans and active duty military members

Education

Family Partnership Charter School September 2016 - Present I Anchorage AK